<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Acr0nim0 Blog</title>
        <link>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Acr0nim0 Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>francosalvucci14@gmail.com (Franco Salvucci)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>francosalvucci14@gmail.com (Franco Salvucci)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 17:28:38 &#43;0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://francosalvucci14.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Thesis</title>
    <link>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/tesi_triennale/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 17:28:38 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Franco Salvucci</author>
    <guid>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/tesi_triennale/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Abstract My undergraduate thesis work focuses on a particular class of graphs, namely temporal graphs. A temporal graph $G=(V,E)$ is a graph where each arc $(u,v)\in E$ is associated with a list of timestamps, which indicate the instants of time in which the arc is active.
My work was to find an efficient algorithm that solves the problem of Temporal Connectivity, that is, to determine whether a given temporal graph with a tree topology is temporally connected or not.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>DataBase Project</title>
    <link>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/database-project/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:30:14 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Franco Salvucci</author>
    <guid>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/database-project/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Intro This is the project I did, in collaboration with my colleagues at the University, for the Database and Knowledge Base (BDC) exam.
The project represents the reality of a taxi company (VroomA), which operates in the Rome area
This is just the database, obviously above the database there is a web interface for users and system administrators
Goals The main objective of this system is to allow users to organize travel by taxi according to their needs, the type of vehicle chosen and the cost of the chosen route.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>WebScraper</title>
    <link>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/webscraper/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:57:30 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Franco Salvucci</author>
    <guid>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/webscraper/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Idea The idea for this project came from a classmate of mine, Simone Zheng.
The idea is to create a scraper that goes to analyze and “study” the data on real estate sites, so as to be able to analyze the various listings, selected by area, and calculate which among the houses/apartments for sale is worth buying and which ones are better not to look at at all
Currently, all the functions that are concerned with calculating which among the listings is the best, based on average salary, IRPEF and tc , are still under development]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>University</title>
    <link>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/universit%C3%A0/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 09:55:54 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Franco Salvucci</author>
    <guid>https://francosalvucci14.github.io/universit%C3%A0/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/Universit%c3%a0/TorVergata.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The university The difficulties Thoughts and advice ]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
